Guide to the Director of Athletics Records, 1939-2007, bulk 1968-2007 UA.13.01.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2019-0087, circa 1990s-2007
  - Correspondence on Recreation Facility Cameron Annex: Tom Butters, 1996 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence on East (Box 28)
  - Fields (Box 28)
  - Pan American Games, 2007 (Box 28)
  - Rebuilding Duke Football (Box 28)
  - The Public and College Football Report (Box 28)
  - Auxiliary Services (Box 28)
  - Correspondence (Box 28)
  - Michael W. Krzyzewski Center (Box 28)
  - Correspondence on West Campus Recreation Facility Cameron Pavilion (Box 28)
  - Correspondence (Box 28)
  - FAR-Faculty Athletics Rep. (Box 28)
  - Correspondence (Box 28)
  - Food Services (Box 28)
  - Duke Football: A Vision for the Future (Box 28)
  - Personnel: General (Box 28)
    Personnel restriction.
  - Ted Leland: Duke Football Program (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous Football Correspondence (Box 29)
  - Correspondence (Box 29)
  - Legends of Golf (Box 29)
  - Legends Correspondence, 1997 (Box 29)
  - National Football Foundation (Box 29)
  - Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 29)
  - Strategic Plan for Duke Athletics (Box 29)
  - A Report on Duke Athletics (Box 29)
  - Staff Meetings and Memos (Box 29)
  - Board of Trustees, 1997 (Box 29)
    Board of Trustees restriction until 2047.
  - Student Athlete Development (Box 29)
  - Student Athlete Report #6 (Box 29)
  - Student Athlete Reports/Writing and Reading (Box 29)
  - Varsity Squash (Box 29)
  - Student Athlete Report-Thompson (Box 29)
  - Special Works (Box 29)
  - Correspondence (Box 29)
  - Administrative Council (Box 29)
  - Alumni Affairs (Box 29)
  - Athletic Council, 2 folders (Box 29)